Seyed Ali Elyasi

Tehran County, Tehran, Iran



s.alielyasi@gmail.com



+989378728706



linkedin.com/in/seyedalielyasi

Summary

Experienced Software Testing Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Functional Testing, Test Strategy, and Test Case Generation. Sound knowledge in SDLC, STCL and Agile methodologies. Well versed in Regression testing, Smoke/ Sanity testing and Usability testing. Strong quality assurance professional with a Bachelor of Engineering focused in Computer Software Engineering from Islamic Azad University North Tehran Branch.

Experience



★ Test Automation Engineer

شييور | Sheypoor Mar 2021 - Present (3 months +)



Software Testing Specialist

Map Jul 2020 - Mar 2021 (9 months)



Map

Apr 2020 - Jul 2020 (4 months)

Education



Islamic Azad University North Tehran Branch

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Software Engineering 2018 - 2022

Licenses & Certifications



Python 3 - SoloLearn

#1073-18548413



🌎 **SQL Fundamentals** - SoloLearn

#1060-18548413



ISTQB - Certified Tester Foundation Level(CTFL) - SEMATEC

8680780

Skills

Test Automation • Manual Testing • Robot Framework • Software Testing • Agile Methodologies • Functional Testing • Quality Assurance • Scrum • Kanban • Test Strategy